<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results on AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling decision making in manufacturing industry with AI</title>
    <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results on AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling decision making in manufacturing industry with AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aicuedatalab.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vispect AI - Visual Inspection Using AI</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/vispect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/vispect/</guid>
      <description>Visual Inspection using AIImprove Inspection Effectiveness with AI assisted inspectionIncrease flexibility with deskilling - No locking for part wise skill foroperators or trained inspectorsCut inspection effort, time and costsMaintain records in cloud for audit and future customer requestLow investment - Economical at low volumes ... From SME to Tier 1 to OEMsRange of volumesLow volume production sometimes... at just 50 per monthSporadic production - such as seasonal or defense productsHigh volume linked to conveyor line capture and inspectionRange of industry typesRange of industry - Automotive Tier 1, Sheet metal, Fabrication, Electrical, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/about/</guid>
      <description>VisionEnable decision making with data science to ensure business results and bring easy to use productsto all front linersCore ValuesFocus on Value to Customer, not revenue or marginsFairness, Sincerity and Integrity before growth and profits.Develop and Adopt a way of management to Assure Quality - The aiCue waySustainability is more important than short term gains. Sustainability isacross social, economic andenvironment and focussed on building organizational processes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/terms/</guid>
      <description>TERMS OF SERVICE OVERVIEW This website is operated by AICUE DATA LAB. Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to AICUE DATA LAB. AICUE DATA LAB offers this website, including all information, tools and services available from this site to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.
By visiting our site and/ or purchasing something from us, you engage in our “Service” and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”, “Terms”), including those additional terms and conditions and policies referenced herein and/or available by hyperlink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AIDeal - AI enabled automotive marketing intelligence from AICUE DATA LAB</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/aideal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/aideal/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to ...Improve sales effectivenessIncrease service labour and parts revenueCut costsReduce InventorySales and StockPredictive reports - Custom Funnel Forecast using AI at segment and region/area level, Customers likelyto buy based on AIVisual reports - Daily sales against LMTD, Daily StockServicePredictive reports - Customers/chassis likely to become inactive, high value jobs likely, service dueVisual reports - Daily Labour , parts by segment/region, Daily ROT (Repair Operation Time) and trendMembershipPredictive reports - Customer upsell queries (for service to membership), Customers likely to buy basedon AISales, Service and Membership - Analytics andAI based predictive intelligenceProven solution - One of Indias large dealership for more than a year and in 2 business linesPay as you go subscription - Large and small dealerships with no upfront investmentsPayback in less than 3 months[Conservative]Action oriented - Delivered at point of use(email / whatsapp and web) at cluster, region, branch or segmentexecutiveStrong user pull - 2000+ hits per week, asked not to stop despite costs in survey, 100s of quick actionemails/whatsapps and proven resultsNo retraining on IT despite older/fresh workforce, No new infrastructure (served from cloud) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AISee - Vision enabled (CCTV) AI and IOT for productivity measurement from AICUE DATA LAB</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/aisee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/aisee/</guid>
      <description>Your AI Supervisor... Smart, Accurate, and TirelessAn AI and IOT solution that enables you to measure productivity with just your CCTV at alow cost monthly subscription.
Productivity to Profitability...Is bottleneck machine running?Is operator available in all stations?Is the truck parked in the dock more than 2 hours?Is there clutter in the main aisles?... and many moreAISee solves challenges with manual supervision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Loading…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us. It is AICUE DATA LAB Private Limited&#39;s policy to respect your privacy regardingany information we may collect from you across our website, http://www.aicuedatalab.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair andlawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will beused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling manufacuring companies with AI for business results</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/solutions/</guid>
      <description>Solutions covering several areas - withDomain experienceAreaExperienceDesign and TestingTest validity - telemetryDrive cycle signaturesTest variant optimizationServiceAbuse detection based on vehicle / machine telematics, Driver ratingPredictivemaintenanceWith Quality teams onwarranty analysis and predictionanomaly detectionearly warningfrom job cardMarketingCustomer segmentation and principal componentsProduct segmentation drivers and trend predictionForecasting at various aggregation levelsBuying/Loss propensityFunnel analysis (and anomaly detection)ManufacturingMachine downtime prediction, Predictive maintenance,Abuse detectionIn use optimization of machine setting/ parameters for operations (such as based on wear, tool /job based learning)Productivity measurement for people, Yield, energy and throughput prediction (and explain-ability)QualityPoka yoke / defect detection ,Measurement with pictures / lasersPre-delivery inspection with drone / fixed cameras (No experience)Test bed data - anomaly detection ,EOL testing optimization for configured productsSourcing and Supply ChainSupply chain risk (line stoppages) prediction (No experience)Price discovery based on master data NLP, Automated LPP from part description for VEPart description based or Geometry based search for standardization (No experience)Support functionsHR Analytics and ML - Joiners and attrition predictionFinance - Collection analytics</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
