<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Control on AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling decision making in manufacturing industry with AI</title>
    <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/tags/quality-control/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quality Control on AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling decision making in manufacturing industry with AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.aicuedatalab.com/tags/quality-control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How a Tier 1 Supplier Cut Inspection Time by 95% Using VISPECT</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/blog/tier-1-commercial-vehicle-quality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/blog/tier-1-commercial-vehicle-quality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-tier-1-suppliers-journey-from-15-minute-inspections-to-45-seconds&#34;&gt;A Tier 1 Supplier&amp;rsquo;s Journey from 15-Minute Inspections to 45 Seconds&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world of commercial vehicle manufacturing, quality assurance is non-negotiable. For one Tier 1 supplier specializing in &lt;strong&gt;fabrication and metal forming&lt;/strong&gt;, ensuring precision across thousands of parts per month was a serious operational challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before VISPECT, their most complex part—requiring &lt;strong&gt;five different views and 150 individual part identification checks&lt;/strong&gt;—took around &lt;strong&gt;15 minutes&lt;/strong&gt; to inspect manually. This created delays, fatigue, and inconsistencies across operators and shifts. Also, this was with an experienced operator, who could only inspect a limited number of parts per hour.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Solution to Quality Control Crisis in Manufacturing SMEs</title>
      <link>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/blog/vispect_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.aicuedatalab.com/blog/vispect_intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-future-of-visual-inspection-is-here&#34;&gt;The Future of Visual Inspection is Here&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this: a new operator walks onto your factory floor and begins performing complex visual inspections with the&#xA;precision of a seasoned quality engineer. This isn’t science fiction—it’s real, thanks to AI-powered visual inspection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;AICUE Data Lab&lt;/strong&gt;, we created &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aicuedatalab.com/vispect&#34;&gt;VISPECT&lt;/a&gt; to address one of the most persistent challenges in manufacturing:&#xA;maintaining consistent, high-quality inspection despite a shortage of skilled labor and increasing product complexity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
