<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industry 4.0 on AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling decision making in manufacturing industry with AI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/industry-4.0/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Industry 4.0 on AICUE DATA LAB - Enabling decision making in manufacturing industry with AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/industry-4.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Audit Readiness Made Simple — Show Numbers, Not Narratives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/audit-readiness-made-simple-show-numbers-not-narratives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/audit-readiness-made-simple-show-numbers-not-narratives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Audits often come down to one big question: &lt;em&gt;Can you demonstrate improvement?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Most shop floors struggle here — safety logs are inconsistent, and human observation is unreliable over long periods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AISee changes that.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Every deviation is logged automatically, along with time-stamped images and compliance percentages.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;When an auditor asks, you don’t show manual registers — you show &lt;strong&gt;data&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;charts&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;trends&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits&#34;&gt;Benefits&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Real-time, quantitative evidence for safety compliance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automatic monthly and quarterly summaries&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Visual proof of CAPA (Corrective and Preventive Actions) effectiveness&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AISee gives you the ability to say with confidence:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Solution to Quality Control Crisis in Manufacturing SMEs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-ai-solution-to-quality-control-crisis-in-manufacturing-smes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-ai-solution-to-quality-control-crisis-in-manufacturing-smes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-future-of-visual-inspection-is-here&#34;&gt;The Future of Visual Inspection is Here&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this: a new operator walks onto your factory floor and begins performing complex visual inspections with the&#xA;precision of a seasoned quality engineer. This isn’t science fiction—it’s real, thanks to AI-powered visual inspection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;AICUE Data Lab&lt;/strong&gt;, we created &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/vispect&#34;&gt;VISPECT&lt;/a&gt; to address one of the most persistent challenges in manufacturing:&#xA;maintaining consistent, high-quality inspection despite a shortage of skilled labor and increasing product complexity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
